StreamReader defaults to UTF-8 encoding unless specified otherwise, instead of defaulting to the ANSI code page
 for the current system. UTF-8 handles Unicode characters correctly and provides consistent results on localized versions
 of the operating system. If you get the current character encoding using the CurrentEncoding property, 
the value is not reliable until after the first Read method, 
since encoding auto detection is not done until the first call to a Read method.
By default, a StreamReader is not thread safe. See TextReader.Synchronized for a thread-safe wrapper.
The Read(Char[], Int32, Int32) and Write(Char[], Int32, Int32) method overloads read and write the number
 of characters specified by the count parameter. These are to be distinguished from BufferedStream.
Read and BufferedStream.Write, which read and write the number of bytes specified by the count parameter.
 Use the BufferedStream methods only for reading and writing an integral number of byte array elements.